Facilities Management Department fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
Facilities Management Department fonds
1960 - 2003
F-11
14.26 m of textual records and other material
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department Maggie Benston Student Services Building, Rm. 0400 8888 University Dr. Burnaby British Columbia Canada V5A 1S6 Telephone: 778.782.3805 Email: archives@sfu.ca http://www.sfu.ca/archives
Facilities Services
The origin of Facilities Management can be traced back to the appointment of the University's first staff member, Arthur Gordon Orr, as Superintendent of Engineering Services on 1 September 1963. By September 1964, the position was renamed Manager of General Services. In 1968, the Department of Physical Plant and Planning was created to manage one of the functions of General Services. In 1988, Physical Plant and Planning was replaced by Facilities Management.
General Services was originally responsible for building construction and plant maintenance, as well as for many other services such as traffic, security, fire prevention, purchasing, bookstore operations, central stores, mail, and food services. Some services, such as food, security, and building cleaning, were contracted to outside firms. In these cases, the Department acted in an overall supervisory role. Other functions, such as purchasing, were carried out by departmental employees. The scheduling of space was an important concern of the new university, and the Manager chaired a Space Usage Committee, charged with room allocation.
In August 1967, General Services was reorganized into three sections: Physical Plant and Planning, Purchasing, and Ancillary Services. The following year, these sections became departments, the heads of which reported to the Vice-President, Administration. Physical Plant and Planning, headed by a Director, was responsible for the maintenance and operations of physical plant, the planning of all future facilities, and the construction of all facilities. These duties included liaison with the faculty on space problems. Ancillary Services was responsible for such functions as food services, security, and mail. Purchasing was charged with purchasing supplies and equipment.
In 1972, Physical Plant and Planning was formally divided into three separate divisions: Planning and Design, Construction, and Maintenance and Operations. The functions of these divisions were outlined in a l973 report, "Organizations, Responsibilities, and Objectives: Physical Plant and Planning." The Planning and Design Division was authorized "to co-ordinate planning and design for the physical development of the university." Construction Division was made responsible "for managing, on behalf of the University, the programme involving the expenditure of capital funds for the construction of new buildings and facilities, as well as designated minor projects." This function included liaison with departmental user groups.
Maintenance and Operations, the largest division, was comprised of various sections: Building and Grounds, Mechanical and Plumbing, Electrical Section, Projects (responsible for estimating and scheduling Work Orders), Maintenance and Operations Office, and Janitorial and Safety. In addition to regular maintenance work carried out by all sections, Projects section estimated and scheduled work orders, which were then carried out by tradespeople from the various sections. At the start of the 1974-1975 fiscal year, the three sections were reduced to two due to the amalgamation of the Planning and Design and Construction sections.
Ancillary Services supervised a number of functions. From 1974-1983, it was responsible for purchasing, duplicating, telephone, mail, traffic and security, central stores, and food services. From 1974-1979, it was also responsible for athletics and recreation, and from 1976-1979 for safety. In December 1983, Ancillary Services was dissolved as a separate unit, and Physical Plant and Planning assumed responsibility for several of Ancillary Services' functions: traffic and security, central stores, campus mail, telephones, and office equipment.
On 1 February 1986, Physical Plant and Planning began to report to the newly created position of Executive Director, Administrative Services, the successor to the Vice-President, Administration. During that year the Department was divided into three different units: Physical Plant, Facilities Planning and Construction, and Support Services. The responsibility for traffic and security was moved to Student Services. In 1988, Facilities Management was created to assume the functions formerly carried out by Physical Plant, and Facilities Planning and Construction.
published
Full
Revised
Title of the fonds is based on the name of its creator.
The Facilities Management fonds consists of records created and received in the course of the administration of the Department and the carrying out of its functions, which changed over time. The original responsibilities of the department included building the physical plant of the University, maintaining buildings and grounds, and providing support services such as food, traffic control, and security. Later, its functions were narrowed to the construction and maintenance of the physical plant and grounds.
The activities documented include policy and procedures development; the planning, construction and maintenance of the University's physical plant and grounds, including land acquisition and liaison with outside consultants and bodies; and the planning and delivery of services to the University, including water and power, traffic, security, fire prevention, purchasing, bookstore operations, central stores, mail, and food. The types of documents include meeting agenda and minutes, certificates, contracts, correspondence, copies of deeds, legal releases, lists, maps, memoranda, architectural plans, reports, and design specification books.
The fonds was arranged into series and originally described by the archivist in 1991. In most cases, records were arranged according to original order and the creating office's classification system. Exceptions are noted in the appropriate series description.
Buildings and structures
The records in Series 1 through 4 were transferred directly to Archives from Facilities Management through the regular application of university Records Retention Schedules and Disposal Authorities (RRSDAs).
The records in Series 5 "Architectural design reports, maps, and plans" were added to the fonds by the archivist in 2006 as an artificial series. The records had been acquired by the archives over a period of years from unrecorded sources and had not been formally processed.
Additional material has been accessioned but not yet processed (as of February 2006: 21 m., 1962-1991). Please consult the archivist for information about using these materials; restrictions may apply. Further accruals are expected.
Some materials have been digitized and are available for offline delivery. See [series 5-1](f-11-5-1) and [series 5-3](f-11-5-3); consult the reference archivist for more information.
For other architectural records relating to construction at SFU, refer to the finding aids of Vice-President, Finance and Administration (F-28), Ron Baker fonds (F-34), Robert Harris fonds (F-46), Zoltan Kiss fonds (F-48), and Student Services fonds (F-107).
Some files may contain personal or confidential information. Access to these files may be restricted as required by law. Files marked 'pending review' must be reviewed by an archivist prior to release, and as a result of the review access restrictions may apply. Please see the file lists and consult the archivist for more details.
File lists are available.
- General office files, 1963 - 1984; F-11-1; 7.68 m of textual records
  published
  Series consists of records relating to the broad mandate of Facilities Management and its many activities, including the planning, construction and maintenance of physical plant and grounds, and the planning and delivery of services to the University. It includes meeting agenda and minutes, certificates, contracts, correspondence, copies of deeds, lists, maps, memoranda, plans, and reports.
  Access to records in the series "Barristers and solicitors" is restricted in accordance with Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy legislation. Consult the unit list and the archivist for further information.
  - Correspondence, 1966 - 1969; F-11-1-1; 5 cm of textual records
    - Outgoing correspondence, 1966; F-11-1-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
      Textual records
      Pending review
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1967; F-11-1-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Outgoing Correspondence, 1969; F-11-1-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Dept. Correspondence - Misc., 1968; F-11-1-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Dept. Correspondence - Bursar's Office, 1968; F-11-1-1-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
  - Administrative activities, 1964 - 1970; F-11-1-2; 24 cm of textual records
    Space Allocation and Planning Committee
    - Accommodation - Space Usage (10-010-1), vol. 1, 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Accommodation - Space Usage (10-010-1), vol. 2, 1966; F-11-1-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Accommodation - Space Usage (10-010-1), vol. 3, 1967 - 1968; F-11-1-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Accommodation - Space (General) (10-010-01), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Accommodation - Moves of Office (10-010-3), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Accommodation - Residences (10-010 - 4), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Budget Misc. (10-020 - 3), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Inventory Budget (10-020-5), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-1)
    - Committees - Space Usage, V.I (10-035-6), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Committees - Space Usage, V.II (10-035-6), 1966 - 1968; F-11-1-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Govt. Burnaby (10-070-2), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Misc. [memos and corr.] (10-130-1), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Misc. (10-130-1), 1968; F-11-1-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Adelman's Report [SFU Housing] (10-130-2), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Personnel - Job Descriptions (10-160-1), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Personnel - Staff Organization, G.S. (10-160-3), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Personnel - Union and Labour Relations Agreement (10-160-5), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Purchasing - SFU Purchasing (10-168-1), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Personnel - Clerk of Works (10-160-11), 1967; F-11-1-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Stores - General Stores (10-190-1), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Students - Misc. (10-195-2), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - University Tours and Functions - Outside Organizations (10-215-2), 1965 - 1968; F-11-1-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Opening Ceremonies (10-010-04), 1965; F-11-1-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Budget (10-020-03), 1968 - 1969; F-11-1-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Correspondence - Progress Certificate (10-020-26), 1969; F-11-1-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Administration Committee [De Vries' File] (10-030-06), 1966 - 1970; F-11-1-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Space Usage Committee (10-030-14), 1968; F-11-1-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - President's Advisory Committee [De Vries' File] (10-030-20), 1968; F-11-1-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Space Sub-Committee (10-030-22), 1966 - 1968; F-11-1-2-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Professional Foundations Centre (10-050-34), 1969 - 1970; F-11-1-2-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Departmental Organization (10-080-35), 1968 - 1970; F-11-1-2-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
  - Outside organizations, 1967 - 1971; F-11-1-3; 3 cm of textual records
    Burnaby Fish and Game Club; Coast Marksmen Inc; Barnet Rifle Club
    - Burnaby Fish and Game Club (20-010-02), 1967 - 1969; F-11-1-3-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Coast Marksmen Inc. (20-010-03), 1969; F-11-1-3-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-2)
    - Barnet Rifle Club (20-010-4), 1969 - 1971; F-11-1-3-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
    - Handrails (20-010-68), 1970; F-11-1-3-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-16)
  - Architects and consultants, 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4; 12 cm of textual records
    Erickson, Arthur; Kiss, Zoltan; McNab, Duncan; Lee, Harry; Logan, David; William R. Rhone; Iredale, W. Randle; Massey, Geoffrey
    - Erickson and Massey (20-010-1), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
      Restricted in part
    - Zoltan Kiss (20-010-3), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - McNab, Lee and Logan (20-010-4), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - Rhone and Ireland (20-010-5), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - Consulting Engineers (20-010-6), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
      Open, no restrictions
      Access review (Jun 10, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Landscaping Consultant (20-010-7), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - Management Consultant (20-010-8), 1965; F-11-1-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - Architectural Competition (20-010-9), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
      Open with enclosures
      Access review (Jun 17, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes 1 documents that contains the personal information of identifiable individuals (medical/psychological history). The restricted document has been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Architects' Fees (20-010-10), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
      Access review (Jun 9, 2022) – The bulk of the file is open. However, it includes a small number of documents (2) that contain restricted confidential information (legal advice). Closed records have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open.
    - Design Directives (20-010-11), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
    - Architects' Misc. Corr. (20-010-12), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-4-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
      Open
      Access review (Jun 9, 2022) – File is open, no restricted information identified.
    - Critical Path Methods (20-010-13), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-4-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-3)
  - Buildings, 1963 - 1968; F-11-1-5; 58 cm of textual records
    Shell Canada Ltd
    - Academic Quadrangle (20-020-1), vol. 1, 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-4)
    - Academic Quadrangle (20-020-1), vol. 2, 1966; F-11-1-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-4)
    - Academic Quadrangle (20-020-1), vol. 3, 1968; F-11-1-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-4)
    - Gymnasium (20-020-1), 1964 - 1968; F-11-1-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-4)
    - Library - Vol. I (20-020-3), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-5-0-5 (Archival box - small 11-5)
    - Library - Vol. II (20-020-3), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-6 (Archival box - small 11-5)
    - Library - Vol. III (20-020-3), 1967; F-11-1-5-0-7 (Archival box - small 11-5)
    - Mall (20-020-4), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - Central Mall (20-020-4), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - Men's Residence - Vol. I (20-020-5), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - Men's Residence - Vol. II (20-020-5), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - President's Residence (20-020-6), 1967; F-11-1-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - Women's Residence - Vol. I (20-020-7), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-6)
    - Women's Residence - Vol. II (20-020-7), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-7)
    - Science Complex - Vol. I (20-020-8), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 11-7)
    - Science Complex - Vol.II (20-020-8), 1966; F-11-1-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 11-7)
    - Science Complex - Vol.III (20-020-8), 1967 - 1968; F-11-1-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 11-7)
    - Science Complex - Vol.IV (20-020-8), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 11-7)
    - Theatre (20-020-9), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - Service Station (Shell) (20-020-10), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
      Reviewed for access (Dec 5, 2023) – The bulk of the file is open. However, a small number of documents (2) contain the personal information of identifiable individuals (employment history) or confidential information (legal advice). Restricted documents have been removed (enclosed); the rest of the file is open. Some enclosed records may be accessed under a Research Agreement, but the confidential materials are closed; consult the reference archivist for more information.
    - Fire Pump House (20-020-12), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - Classroom Complex (20-020-13), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - Inflammable Stores (20-020-14), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - Building Costs (20-020-17), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - General (20-020-18), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - Phase III Planning, 1967; F-11-1-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
  - Contracts, change orders, and progress certificates, 1963 - 1968; F-11-1-6; 63 cm of textual records
    Erickson, Arthur; BC Hydro; Massey, Geoffrey
    - A.Q. (20-030-1), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - A.Q. Millwork (20-030-1a), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - A.Q. Mezz. Labs Temp (20-030-1b), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - A.Q. Lab Addition (20-030-1c), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-8)
    - A.Q. Phase II (20-030-1.11), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Gymnasium (20-030-2), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Library Phase IIa 5th Floor (20-030-3IIIa), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Library Vol. I (20-030-3), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Library Vol. II (20-030-3), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Library Millwork (20-030-3a), 1965; F-11-1-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Univ. Store Millwork (20-030-3b), 1965; F-11-1-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Central Mall and T.C. (20-030-4), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Central Mall and T.C. - V.II (20-030-4), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Men's Residence (20-030-5), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 11-9)
    - Presidents Residence (20-030-6), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-15 (Archival box - small 11-10)
    - Women's Residence (20-030-7), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-16 (Archival box - small 11-10)
    - Sc.Comp. Furniture (20-030-8IV), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-17 (Archival box - small 11-10)
    - Theatre (20-030-9), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-18 (Archival box - small 11-10)
    - Theatre Modifications (20-030-9a), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-19 (Archival box - small 11-10)
    - Phase I Science Complex (20-030-8), 1964 - 1965; F-11-1-6-0-20 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Phase I Science Complex (20-030-8), 1965 - 1968; F-11-1-6-0-21 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Phase II Science Complex (20-030-8), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-22 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Sc. Comp. Occupancy Inspection Reports (20-030-8), 1966; F-11-1-6-0-23 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Phase III Science Complex (20-030-8II), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-24 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Sc. Comp Lecture Theatre (20-030-8a), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-25 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Sc. Comp. Research Labs (20-030-8b), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-26 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Extension of Services Sc. Comp. (20-030-8d), 1966; F-11-1-6-0-27 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Erickson Massey (20-030-10), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-28 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Site Clearing (20-030-11), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-29 (Archival box - standard 11-11)
    - Grading (20-030-12), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-30 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Landscaping (20-030-13), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-31 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Landscaping Vol.II (20-030-13), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-32 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Landscaping Competition and Maintenance (20-030-13a), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-33 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Roads and Parking Lots (20-030-14), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-34 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Staff Parking Lot (20-030-14a), 1966; F-11-1-6-0-35 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - 1000 Car Parking Lot and Men's Residence Services (20-030-14b), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-36 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Playfield One (20-030-15), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-37 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Water Distribution and System (20-030-17), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-38 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Outside Lighting (20-030-18), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-39 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Sewer Contract (20-030-19), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-40 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Fire Pump House (20-030-20), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-41 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Water Tower Phase I(20-030-21.I), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-42 (Archival box - standard 11-12)
    - Water Tower Phase II (20-030-21.II), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-43 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - BC Hydro Microwave Communication Centre (20-030-22a), 1964 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-44 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - BC Hydro System Control Centre (20-030-22b), 1963 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-45 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Burnaby Mountain BC Hydro System Control Centre (20-030-22c), 1967 - 1968; F-11-1-6-0-46 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Boiler Agreement (20-030-23), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-47 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Boiler and PHW Mains Additions to Mechanical Services (20-030-23a), 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-48 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Archaeology Cartography - Millwork (20-030-24), 1967; F-11-1-6-0-49 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Classroom Complex (20-030-25), 1966 - 1967; F-11-1-6-0-50 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Precast Concrete (20-030-26), 1966; F-11-1-6-0-51 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Bio Depository System (20-030-28), 1963 - 1966; F-11-1-6-0-52 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Lunch Room and Conversion of Student Lounge (20- 030-2a), 1966; F-11-1-6-0-53 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
  - Field and site meetings and deficiency tests, 1964 - 1967; F-11-1-7; 8 cm of textual records
    - Academic Quadrangle (20-060-1), 1965 - 1967; F-11-1-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Gym (20-060-2), 1966; F-11-1-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Library (20-060-3), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 11-13)
    - Mall (20-060-4), 1965 - 1966; F-11-1-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 11-13)